Kaio's late. Again.
But she said she was gonna give me my present today.
Maybe she was up all night making it and overslept.
Satoru?
Yeah.
Yes, sir!
Everything all right?
Or is there something on your mind?
Kaio?
Open up, it's me!
Kaio!
Oh no.
Rubber boot tracks. Too big to be a kid's. It snowed two nights ago. And these tracks are fresh. Whoever was here was an adult. Probably male.
Shit. Now what do we do?
It's the girls festival and we'll have fun.
kissing chill few days.
Number three.
About two.
立ち止まって 振り返って 止めどない今日を嘆き合った
記憶だって 永遠にだって 残らないもんと思い知って
僕がずっとかきむして 心隅っこで泣いた
そしてどうか 失くさないでよって後悔した
過ぎる日々を後悔してんだよって そう言い逃したあの日
君を待った 僕は待った 途切れない明日も過ぎてって
僕は今日もかきむして 忘れない傷をつけてるんだよ
忘れない downloading
忘れないどうなる
忘れない後悔した
忘れないでしょ
あーオウ wins
I didn't go back to school for two days.
Hmm. I guess Mom went to the store.
I found out a kid got snatched not too long ago, over in the next town.
But the cops already caught that scumbag.
This guy is someone new. We have to warn people before he does it again.
The problem is the police put a gag order on the story.
What about airing it when kids aren't watching?
The station could do that easy.
And I can go talk to the school and see if they'll issue a warning.
Okay. I'll talk to the boss about your idea.
I'd appreciate it.
He's a reporter for Ishikari TV. My mom used to work with him.
The last thing I want is for Satoru to grow up with horrible memories like this.
I hear you.
Making me forget was her idea.
I know you're worried, but you've got to eat something.
What happened isn't your fault, kiddo.
I tried, but I couldn't help her.
I don't know about that.
I just... I didn't want her to be alone.
And thanks to you, she wasn't.
It wasn't enough. I should have done more.
Look, what happened, happened.
So it's pointless to beat yourself up about it.
In a situation like hers, there's only so much anyone could have done.
That goes for you and me.
You should go back to school tomorrow.
You'll just feel worse staying here alone.
Okay.
Good.
Now eat up, okay?
Yeah.
I, uh, have a confession.
The other day I told you Kaio was home with a cold.
That's not true.
She's staying with her grandmother in Sapporo for personal reasons.
It happened so fast, she didn't have a chance to say goodbye.
But don't worry. I hear she's doing well.
She ran away.
I heard Kaio's mom hit her with a broom.
Oh my god, really?
Hey, it's better she's with her grandma.
Hey, Satoru!
Cheer up, man!
Yeah, don't worry. You'll see her again.
Mm-hmm.
Satoru, the school and the PTA talked about it and decided this was for the best.
I hate to ask this, but could you go along with the story?
Sure.
I'm sorry.
The press couldn't talk about it either.
And for the past few days, the police had a car parked outside Kaio's house.
They were watching it because they pegged her mom as the prime suspect.
Then, six days after Kaio disappeared.
Listen up, everyone. I have an announcement.
From now on, when you leave school, make sure you're either with your parents...
The next girl was kidnapped sooner than she should have been.
You hear about Aya Nakanishi?
I don't know if you knew her, but she was a student at Izumi Elementary.
I heard.
I have a friend who goes there, and he said she ran away to go live with her grandfather.
She did, huh? Just like Kaio.
She didn't run away. That's a lie.
If you ask me, there's a kidnapper on the loose.
The details might not be exactly the same, but things were definitely following the same flow of time as before.
Stations ran stories on the missing girls all day, except Ishikari TV.
They only ran them early in the morning and late at night.
So, parents were advised to have their kids watch Ishikari TV only.
I'm home!
After Aya Nakanishi went missing, I noticed something.
The cops had dialed back their stakeout at Kaio's place.
They must have realized a serial kidnapper was on the loose.
Ten days after Kaio disappeared, I saw her mom toss out a bag of trash.
A pair of mittens was in it.
I'll give you your present tomorrow.
Promise.
Where am I?
I'm back in 2006 again.
Address 23-1, 4th Street.
Victim, Sachiko Fujinuma.
Femus, 52.
Suspect is her son, Satoru Fujinuma, 29.
We're talking to the eyewitness now.
Over.
Are you Satoru Fujinuma?
No.
It wasn't me.
I didn't do it.
God damn it.
I couldn't save Kaio.
Mom's still dead.
Everyone still thinks I killed her.
I couldn't change anything after all.
Only one thing to do.
Run.
I'm hiding under a bridge in a box.
Talk about cliches.
I wonder if I made the news yet.
Come on, think.
Why was Mom murdered?
Did she know who the killer was?
When I found her, I didn't see her phone anywhere.
Or her bag.
They were both gone.
The killer took them.
But why?
I bet she had evidence on him, and he was scared the cops would find it.
I'm crashing hard.
If I only had a day to sleep, I'd think better.
There you go.
Eat up.
Thanks.
I'm sorry about work today.
It's no big deal.
One no-show won't get you fired.
Irie was worried about you, though.
Well, I wasn't, because I figured you had a pretty good reason.
We can talk about it after we eat.
Thanks.
That sucks.
The fight with your mom was that bad, huh?
Yeah.
That's the trouble with old folks.
They could be hella stubborn.
You can crash here as long as you want, but your mom's your mom, so try and patch things
up with her.
I will.
Hey, you want a beer?
No.
Crap, I'm all out.
I'm going to go out and get some more.
He's kind of a knob, but his heart's in the right place.
I feel bad for lying.
Police rushed to the apartment after receiving an anonymous tip.
Inside, they found the body of a woman believed to be the tenant's mother.
The suspect, described as a male in his late 20s, fled the scene before he could be questioned.
The police are currently searching the neighborhood for him.
This is not good.
This is so not good.
And now the sports minute.
Japan's soccer team is heading for the playoffs in Germany today for what some are calling
the most anti-
I should have known he'd screw me over.
What am I saying?
I can't blame him.
He was just trying to do the right thing.
If I was in his shoes, I'd do the same.
God damn it.
You're an idiot.
Irie?
No way!
You called me by my first name?
That's a first.
You know, if you're on the run, you shouldn't leave your phone on.
The police can use GPS to track you.
Oh.
Are you just gonna sit there?
Hop on, let's go.
Come on, shake a leg.
Sorry about this, Katagiri.
Call me Irie.
It's one of the perks of writing Tandem.
I can't believe you let me in your house.
You do know why they're after me, right?
The cops came to see the manager today.
I overheard them talking about it.
It was on the news, too.
Then why'd you risk helping me get away?
Because you didn't kill her, that's why.
At dinner, I could see how much you guys meant to each other.
That's a fact.
Yeah, well, thank you.
You don't have to thank me.
I can't imagine what you're going through and to have the cops after you, too.
You don't deserve that.
No one deserves the kind of stuff you've been through before, either.
What?
This.
You left it behind at work the other day.
One of the chapters had a sticky, so I went ahead and read it.
Talked all about what happened in your hometown when you were a kid.
How Kyo Hinazuki was murdered.
I cried when I read it.
She died the day of the girls' festival.
Wait, it says that?
Yeah.
It says she died on March 3rd.
Anyway, make yourself at home.
I have to take the bike back before they miss it.
And don't even think about leaving this room.
This isn't how it was before.
It changed.
I changed it.
If I can go back again, I can save Kyo.
Oh, yeah.
I'm in Irie's room.
Dear Satorial,
I think I should stick to my normal schedule today,
so I'm going to work my usual shift.
The fam said they'd be leaving the house around 10
and won't be coming back till after 8 tonight.
The key to the house and my bike are next to my clock.
Here's the number to my cell.
Wait.
I thought her last name was Katagiri.
Thank you, Mr. Nishizono.
I can't tell you how much we appreciate it.
Well, your father's done so much for me.
I wish I could do more.
Oh, God, no.
Believe me, you've done enough.
Heck, my dad couldn't be happier.
Thanks to that stoplight and crosswalk you approved,
we get more customers now than ever before.
Please.
Your business is doing well
because your father is a shrewd businessman.
All I did was give him a little boost.
That's all.
Besides, it's a school route.
Safety first, you know?
The city council's been talking about
putting a stoplight here for ages.
I left the receipts by the till.
Heading home.
Sure.
Nice hustle today, Irie.
What you got there?
Oh, just some leftover pizza.
Leftovers?
Are you kidding?
Go on, get a fresh one.
My treat.
Thanks for the offer, boss.
But this'll do.
My friend won't know the difference anyway.
Oh, I hope she likes it then.
That is if your friend's a, you know, girl.
Yeah, well, see you tomorrow.
She's a cute girl, huh?
Yeah, I guess.
If you're into that sort of thing.
I mean, she's 17.
She's just a kid.
Yeah, well, I should get back to the office.
Thanks for stopping by, sir.
Hey, Irie!
What's up?
Here.
You forgot to take this.
It is part of the promotion, after all.
Oh, okay, thanks.
I was wondering,
have you talked to Satoru lately?
No.
I can't believe he'd just up and kill his own...
I mean, you know, what they're saying he did.
It's not like the guy at all.
No, it isn't.
I don't know how tight you guys were,
but if you see him,
do what you can to help him, okay?
Sure.
Let him know we're on his side.
And if you talk to him, give me a shout.
Yeah, I totally will.
What am I doing?
I doubt I'm going to find anything.
A kid disappeared here three years ago.
Yeah, I think I remember this.
And three weeks later, they arrested some guy for it.
Even after the trial, he swore he was innocent.
It's a hell of a coincidence.
Or is it?
Why would you want to go and call the police for?
Iri...
Is that why you wanted me to help Satoru?
You said you were on his side.
You said that!
Wait a sec, Iri.
I just...
I was worried about you, that's all.
If all you wanted was to get him caught,
you should have told me the truth!
I trusted you!
I trusted you and you lied to me!
I didn't want to see you get hurt.
I swear.
That, I believe.
I'm sorry.
Boss, please.
If you're really worried about me,
then don't call the police over here.
I don't want my family getting involved in this.
I'm sorry, Satoru.
Nah, it's no big deal.
I got to sleep a bit.
So thanks for letting me stay and conk out on your floor.
No, don't mention it.
I just wish you could go back.
It's okay.
It's better if I don't.
By the way, that's not your parents' house, is it?
Uh-uh.
I'm staying with my uncle and his wife.
My town doesn't have a high school.
It's out in the boonies,
so I had to come to the city for it.
I asked my uncle,
and he said I could stay with them in Chiba.
Mind if I ask a weird question?
Uh-uh.
Like, why do you believe me?
You don't even know me all that well.
You're right, I don't.
But I don't care.
I want to believe you.
When I was in elementary school,
my dad took me grocery shopping one day.
The owner stopped my dad
and accused him of stealing a candy bar.
Like I said, my town's small,
so the owner knew my dad.
He said if he just admitted stealing it,
he'd drop the whole thing.
But he refused,
and the owner kept pushing him.
I never heard my dad yell before,
but that day he went off.
The owner ended up calling the police,
and since my dad belonged to the local farmer's co-op,
they gave him a three-month suspension as punishment.
You didn't steal it, Daddy!
I know!
I saw you didn't do anything wrong!
After what happened,
Dad quit the co-op,
divorced Mom,
and left.
I guess my mom thought he really stole it,
like everyone else in town.
If someone believes in you,
you're not alone.
And if I was in your situation,
I'd want someone to believe me.
I think you should go home.
Tell the cops I forced you to hide me.
They'll buy that story.
God, you're an idiot.
You can't deal with this on your own,
and I won't lie to the police.
Okay, but could you not call me an idiot anymore?
No promises.
I'll be back in a sec
with a change of clothes and stuff for you.
The boss didn't call the police after all.
Good for him.
Hmm?
But it can't be.
What is this?
It can't be from him
because he told me his mom's phone was gone.
Unless he found it.
No.
It's from the killer.
He's after me now.
Oh my God.
Gotta get out.
I gotta...
僕だけが見てた君のこと 過去も未来も 悲しみも喜びも すべて
大人になるってきっと 優しくなることだと信じていた
子供の頃も僕のままに 君のこと守りたいと思う
暗闇から目覚めても 僕を待ち受けてる
彼方で二人を隠した この街に
誰も知らない 雪が降っていた
君は僕の胸に 刻まれた一番深い 傷跡のようで
君が笑う この世界の歌 乗り戻すよ